All right, you're done. I hope you don't mind that I gave you
the larger table this time. But it depends on the first one, so it would've been
hard to give you in any other order. I gave you the content value structure, so
it's pretty easy to just insert the data. Then, we query the data back out.
[SOUND] If move to first fails, the cursor is empty, and
the query failed. [LAUGH] Lots of cut and paste here. It is nice to fetch the dv
values using the helper for the data type, although its not strictly necessary,
since we know our test data is actually going to match our constrains. And
there is one more failure case we need to add here, if our query doesn't return
any rows. And that's it. All that just to get a database and
a way to test it. Now let's run the test again. Well, at
least we know all the basic stuff works, and just remember, without these tests,
you wouldn't have been able to run this code for a very, very long time.